Wow
うわぁ
...
Bucon?
ブ コンか
Wait a minute, that's amazing.
ちょっと待って、すごいね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Let's say it with a nice face, then.
良い顔で言おう、じゃあ
What, no?
え、ダメ?
why?
なんで?
Have you never done it?
したことないの?
do not have.
ない
lie?
嘘?
Seriously?
まじで?
Eh.
えー
You should do it now.
もうすればいいじゃん
I might not have any rubber today.
ゴムないかも、今日
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Please look for it.
探してくれ
Great, wait a minute.
すげえ、ちょっと待って
Long time no see.
久々
But wait a minute.
なんだけど、ちょっと待って
This is a little.
これ、ちょっと
It really makes me laugh.
本当に笑うとしてる
Wait a minute.
ちょっと、あれ
I'll put it on, just a little.
つけるね、ちょっと
It's been a while though.
久々なんだけど
I don't wear it, but always.
俺、つけないんだけど、いつも
lowest.
最低
Like an allergy.
アレルギーみたいな
thank you.
ありがとう
Did you put it on?
つけた?
Look.
ほら
Is that okay?
それでいい?
good?
いい?
Don't say it's the worst.
最低とか言わないで
Do it.
やって
Does it feel good?
気持ちよくね?
Is there no dakoto?
だことない?
Open your legs.
足開いて
oh yeah.
そうそう
Please hand it over.
差し付け出してください
Grrrr.
グ ーッと
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
Can I put a lot on my face?
顔にいっぱいかけていい?